Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG 42.5
New York University Archives
- Series I: Exhibition Files, 1961-1988
  - William Brice -- A Selection of Painting and Drawing, 1947-1986 (Box I:7, Folder 30)
  - William Brice -- Press Release, 1986 July-October (Box I:7, Folder 31)
  - William Brice -- Press Reviews, 1986 August-1987 March (Box I:7, Folder 32)
  - Jaar/Sheehan -- Press Release, 1987 January (Box I:7, Folder 33)
  - Sheehan, Maura, 1985-1987 (Box I:7, Folder 34)
  - Jaar, Alfredo, 1986-1988 (Box I:7, Folder 35)
  - Rick Horton -- Small Gallery Exhibition (January 20-February 28, 1987), 1986-1987 (Box I:7, Folder 36)
  - Harrisons -- Correspondence, 1986 April-November (Box I:7, Folder 37)
  - Harrisons -- Curriculum Vitae and Exhibition List, 1986 October-1987 September (Box I:7, Folder 38)
  - Harrisons -- Press Release, 1987 March (Box I:7, Folder 39)
  - Harrisons -- Transcripts of Conversation, Undated (Box I:7, Folder 40)
  - Harrisons -- Newsletter Conversation, 1987 (Box I:7, Folder 41)
  - Harrison -- Printed Materials, 1982-1985 (Box I:7, Folder 42)
  - Harrisons -- Newsclippings, 1978 February-1986 August (Box I:7, Folder 43)
  - Harrisons -- Reviews, 1987 March-April (Box I:7, Folder 44)
  - Paul Hunter -- White Noise (Small Gallery Exhibition), 1987 March (Box I:7, Folder 45)
  - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Slides and Artists List, 1987 (Box I:7, Folder 46)
  - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Labels, 1987 (Box I:7, Folder 47)
  - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Press Release, 1987 April (Box I:7, Folder 48)
  - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Reviews, 1987 June-September (Box I:7, Folder 49)
  - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Press Kits and Publicity, 1987 (Box I:7, Folder 50)
  - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Miscellaneous, 1987 January-March (Box I:7, Folder 51)
  - Pat Keck (Small Gallery in Conj. with AVA), 1985-1987 (Box I:7, Folder 52)
  - Out of Eastern Europe -- Exhibit Materials, Undated (Box I:7, Folder 53)
  - Out of Eastern Europe -- Invitations and Copy, 1987 (Box I:7, Folder 54)
  - Out of Eastern Europe -- Clippings, 1987 February-1988 January (Box I:7, Folder 55)
  - Out of Eastern Europe -- Press Releases, 1987 February-July (Box I:7, Folder 56)
  - Out of Eastern Europe -- Anna Bohdziewicz, Undated (Box I:7, Folder 57)
  - Ricardo Zulueta -- Tableau Utopia, 1987 February-June (Box I:8, Folder 1)
  - Lee gordon -- The Hooded Paintings (Small Gallery September 14-October 24, 1987), 1987 August-September (Box I:8, Folder 2)
  - Morality Tales -- Press Release, 1987 May-November (Box I:8, Folder 3)
  - Morality Tales -- Artists, 1987 September-1988 April (Box I:8, Folder 4)
  - Morality Tales -- Artists' Bios (1 of 3), 1985-1987 (Box I:8, Folder 5)
  - Morality Tales -- Artists' Bios (2 of 3), 1977-1987 (Box I:8, Folder 6)
  - Morality Tales -- Artists' Bios (3 of 3), 1985-1989 (Box I:8, Folder 7)
  - Morality Tales -- Reviews, 1987 September-1989 January (Box I:8, Folder 8)
  - Morality Tales -- Andy Patton Correspondence, Undated (Box I:8, Folder 9)
  - Morality Tales -- Catalogue Essay, 1985-1986 (Box I:8, Folder 10)
  - Morality Tales -- Exhibition List, Undated (Box I:8, Folder 11)
  - Morality Tales -- ICI Newsletter, 1987 March-August (Box I:8, Folder 12)
  - Morality Tales -- The Idea of the Moral Imperative in Contemporary Art (Tapes), Undated (Box I:8, Folder 13)
  - Juan Gonzalez (Window Installation in Conj. with Morality Tales), 1987 August-October (Box I:8, Folder 14)
  - Ghislaine Vappereau, 1987 (Box I:8, Folder 15)
  - Black Mountain College -- Press Releases, 1987 October (Box I:8, Folder 16)
  - Black Mountain College -- Reviews, 1987 December-1988 February (Box I:8, Folder 17)
  - Black Mountain College -- Exhibition List and Bibliography, 1987 (Box I:8, Folder 18)
  - Black Mountain College -- Performances, 1987 (Box I:8, Folder 19)
  - Black Mountain College -- Recordings List, 1987 November 2-December 19 (Box I:8, Folder 20)
  - Black Mountain College -- Miscellaneous, 1983 January-1987 May (Box I:8, Folder 21)
  - Gaylen Gerber (Small Gallery November 2-December 19, 1987), 1987 September-October (Box I:8, Folder 22)
  - Ching ho Cheng (Window Installation), 1987 September-1988 May (Box I:8, Folder 23)
  - Randolph Black (Window Installation), 1988 January 19-February 27 (Box I:8, Folder 24)
  - Viollet-le-Duc -- Exhibition Checklist, Circa 1987-1988 (Box I:8, Folder 25)
  - Viollet-le-Duc -- Text Panels, Circa 1987-1988 (Box I:8, Folder 26)
  - Viollet-le-Duc -- Labels, Circa 1987-1988 (Box I:8, Folder 27)
  - Viollet-le-Duc -- Press Release, 1987 December (Box I:8, Folder 28)
  - Viollet-le-Duc -- Notices and Reviews, 1988 January-February (Box I:8, Folder 29)
  - Viollet-le-Duc -- Small Glass from the Cloisters (Small Gallery), 1988 January-February (Box I:8, Folder 30)
  - Cecil Beaton -- Lists and Captions, Circa 1987-1988 (Box I:8, Folder 31)
  - Cecil Beaton -- Design Details, Circa 1986-1988 (Box I:8, Folder 32)
  - Cecil Beaton -- Publicity Packet, Circa 1987-1988 (Box I:8, Folder 33)
  - Cecil Beaton -- Posters, Circa 1987-1988 (Box I:8, Folder 34)
  - Cecil Beaton -- Grey Reviews and Lournay Ads (1 of 3), 1988 March-June (Box I:8, Folder 35)
  - Cecil Beaton -- Grey Reviews and Lournay Ads (2 of 3), 1987 December-1988 April (Box I:8, Folder 36)
  - Cecil Beaton -- Grey Reviews and Lournay Ads (3 of 3), 1987 December-1988 May (Box I:8, Folder 37)
  - Cecil Beaton -- Foreign Press, 1986 March-1987 February (Box I:8, Folder 38)
  - Cecil Beaton -- Foreign Press (2 of 2), 1986 May-1987 December (Box I:8, Folder 39)
  - Cecil Beaton -- Mellor Lecture, 1988 February-April (Box I:8, Folder 40)
  - Ann Messner -- Window, 1987 September-November (Box I:8, Folder 41)
  - Rosalind Solomon -- CV, 1988 May (Box I:8, Folder 42)
  - Rosalind Solomon -- Correspondence, 1988 January-1991 May (Box I:8, Folder 43)
  - Rosalind Solomon -- Exhibit Images, 1988 (Box I:8, Folder 44)
  - Rosalind Solomon -- Catalogue (1 of 2), Circa 1988 (Box I:8, Folder 45)
  - Rosalind Solomon -- Catalogue (2 of 2), Circa 1988 (Box I:8, Folder 46)
  - Rosalind Solomon -- Reviews (1 of 2), 1988 May-June (Box I:9, Folder 1)
  - Rosalind Solomon -- Reviews (2 of 2), 1988 May-July (Box I:9, Folder 2)
  - Rosalind Solomon -- Miscellaneous Press, 1988 February-1989 April (Box I:9, Folder 3)
  - Rosalind Solomon -- Research Materials (1 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box I:9, Folder 4)
  - Rosalind Solomon -- Research Materials (2 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box I:9, Folder 5)
  - Rosalind Solomon -- Notes, Circa 1987-1989 (Box I:9, Folder 6)
  - Twelve From New York -- The 1988 Selections, 1988-1989 (Box I:9, Folder 7)
  - Eric Avery -- Works on Paper (Small Gallery), 1987-1988 October (Box I:9, Folder 8)
  - Grey Exhibition Schedule, 1986-1989 (Box I:9, Folder 9)
  - Show and Tell -- Proposal, Undated (Box I:9, Folder 10)
  - Show and Tell -- Press Release, Undated (Box I:9, Folder 11)
  - Show and Tell -- Eisler's List of Items, Undated (Box I:9, Folder 12)
  - Show and Tell -- Lay-Out/Design, 1988 (Box I:9, Folder 13)
  - Show and Tell -- Invitations, Brochures and Other Mailings, 1988 (Box I:9, Folder 14)
  - Show and Tell -- Reviews, 1988 September-October (Box I:9, Folder 15)
  - Show and Tell -- Address Unknown (Video by J. Gianvito), 1986-1988 (Box I:9, Folder 16)
  - Show and Tell -- Miscellaneous, Undated (Box I:9, Folder 17)
  - Landmarks of NY -- Small Gallery (in Conj. with Show and Tell), 1987 June-1988 November (Box I:9, Folder 18)
  - Luc Courchesne -- Encyclopedia Chiaroscuro, 1985-1988, 1988 August-September (Box I:9, Folder 19)
  - Bolek Greczynski -- Windows (Oct 3-Nov 5), 1986 June-1988 November (Box I:9, Folder 20)
  - Adolf Wolfli -- Catalogue, Undated (Box I:9, Folder 21)
  - Adolf Wolfli-- Press Release, 1988 October (Box I:9, Folder 22)
  - Adolf Wolfli -- Reviews, 1988 November-1989 February (Box I:9, Folder 23)
  - Adolf Wolfli -- European Catalogue, 1976-1985 (Box I:9, Folder 24)
  - Adolf Wolfli -- Cassette, Undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Adolf Wolfli -- Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box I:9, Folder 26)
  - Kevin Wolff -- Windows, 1986 September-1988 December (Box I:9, Folder 27)
  - Shelly Bachman -- Small Gallery(Nov-Dec, 1988), 1988-1989 January (Box I:9, Folder 28)
  - Michael Landy, 1988-1989 (Box I:9, Folder 29)
  - Brazilian Art (Cancelled), 1987-1988 (Box I:9, Folder 30)
  - Politics and Polemics -- Press Release, 1988 April-1989 January (Box I:9, Folder 31)
  - Politics and Polemics -- Reviews and Publicity, 1989 January-February (Box I:9, Folder 32)
  - Politics and Polemics -- Lists, 1988-1989 (Box I:9, Folder 33)
  - Politics and Polemics -- Materials (1 of 3), 1988 (Box I:9, Folder 34)
  - Politics and Polemics -- Materials (2 of 3), 1988-1989 (Box I:9, Folder 35)
  - Politics and Polemics -- Materials (3 of 3), 1987-1989 (Box I:9, Folder 36)
  - Masami Teraoka -- Small Gallery (1 of 2), 1976 May-1989 February (Box I:9, Folder 37)
  - Masami Teraoka -- Small Gallery (2 of 2), 1988 September-1989 August (Box I:9, Folder 38)
  - Andy Warhol -- Exhibit Proposal, 1987 July (Box I:9, Folder 39)
  - Andy Warhol -- Bath's Research (1 of 2), Circa 1986-1989 (Box I:9, Folder 40)
  - Andy Warhol -- Bath's Research (2 of 2), Circa 1986-1989 (Box I:9, Folder 41)
  - Andy Warhol -- What Is Success Article, 1949 October (Box I:9, Folder 42)
  - Andy Warhol -- Item Lists, Undated (Box I:9, Folder 43)
  - Andy Warhol -- Old and New Lists, Undated (Box I:9, Folder 44)
  - Andy Warhol -- Photograph List, Undated (Box I:9, Folder 45)
  - Andy Warhol -- Catalogue, CIrca 1986-1989 (Box I:9, Folder 46)
  - Andy Warhol -- Catalogue (1 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box I:10, Folder 1)
  - Andy Warhol -- Catalogue (2 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box I:10, Folder 2)
  - Andy Warhol -- Catalogue Essays (1 of 2), Circa 1987-1989 (Box I:10, Folder 3)
  - Andy Warhol -- Catalogue Essays (2 of 2), 1987-1989 (Box I:10, Folder 4)
  - Andy Warhol -- Exhibit Installation, Circa 1987-1989 (Box I:10, Folder 5)
  - Andy Warhol -- Text Panels and Front Text, Circa 1987-1989 (Box I:10, Folder 6)
  - Andy Warhol -- Text Panel and Labels, Circa 1987-1989 (Box I:10, Folder 7)
  - Andy Warhol -- Press Release, 1989 February (Box I:10, Folder 8)
  - Andy Warhol -- Tinka Swindell Interview, 1988 June 8 (Box I:10, Folder 9)
  - Andy Warhol -- Other Warhol Shows and Lectures, 1986-1989 (Box I:10, Folder 10)
  - Andy Warhol -- Press (Grey) (1 of 3), 1989 November-1990 May (Box I:10, Folder 11)
  - Andy Warhol -- Press (Grey Gallery, 2 of 3), 1989 March-1990 August (Box I:10, Folder 12)
  - Andy Warhol -- Press (Grey Gallery, 3 of 3), 1989 February-May (Box I:10, Folder 13)
  - Andy Warhol -- Press (Carnegie and Cartier), 1989 July-1990 November (Box I:10, Folder 14)
  - Andy Warhol -- Press (Lingotto), 1990 March-May (Box I:10, Folder 15)
  - Andy Warhol -- Press (Serpentine), 1989 July-August (Box I:10, Folder 16)
  - Andy Warhol -- Press (Newport Harbor), 1989 November-1990 May (Box I:10, Folder 17)
  - Andy Warhol -- Invites from Venues, 1989 (Box I:10, Folder 18)
  - Andy Warhol -- Samples of Lupton/Miller Work, 1987-1988 (Box I:10, Folder 19)
  - Zuka -- The French Revolution Through American Eyes (Small Gallery, 1 of 3), 1985-1989 (Box I:10, Folder 20)
  - Zuka -- The French Revolution Through American Eyes (Small Gallery, 2 of 3), 1986-1989 (Box I:10, Folder 21)
  - Zuka -- The French Revolution Through American Eyes (Small Gallery, 3 of 3), 1988 (Box I:10, Folder 22)
  - Mike Bidlo (Window Installation in Conj. with Warhol Exhibit), 1988 (Box I:10, Folder 23)
  - Robert Morris -- Proposal and Other Preliminary Material (1 of 2), 1986-1988 (Box I:10, Folder 24)
  - Robert Morris -- Proposal and Other Preliminary Material (2 of 2), 1986-1989 (Box I:10, Folder 25)
  - Robert Morris -- Correspondence, 1989 January 26-February 2 (Box I:10, Folder 26)
  - Robert Morris -- Press Release, 1989 April 21 (Box I:10, Folder 27)
  - Robert Morris -- Check List, Undated (Box I:10, Folder 28)
  - Robert Morris -- Wall Text, 1989 May 8 (Box I:10, Folder 29)
  - Robert Morris -- Installation, 1989 March-April (Box I:10, Folder 30)
  - Robert Morris -- Catalogue (1 of 3), 1989 March-April (Box I:10, Folder 31)
  - Robert Morris -- Catalogue (2 of 3), Circa 1988-1989 (Box I:10, Folder 32)
  - Robert Morris -- Catalogue (3 of 3), 1989 (Box I:10, Folder 33)
  - Robert Morris -- Reviews, Notices, 1989 May-October (Box I:10, Folder 34)
  - Bernard Frize -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Robert Morris), Circa 1989 (Box I:10, Folder 35)
  - Tom Hardy and Steve Ausbury (Treasures of the Bastille), Circa 1989 (Box I:10, Folder 36)
  - Weegee -- Exhibit Material, Undated (Box I:10, Folder 37)
  - Weegee -- Press, 1989 September-November (Box I:10, Folder 38)
  - Ching Ho Cheng -- Wall Text, Circa 1989 (Box I:11, Folder 1)
  - Peter Levinson (Window Installation and Small Gallery), Circa 1989 (Box I:11, Folder 2)
  - Excommunication -- Press Release, 1989 November 8 (Box I:11, Folder 3)
  - Excommunication -- Text, Circa 1989 (Box I:11, Folder 4)
  - Excommunication -- Text and Other Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box I:11, Folder 5)
  - Excommunication -- Border Arts Workshop, 1989 September-1990 January (Box I:11, Folder 6)
  - Excommunication -- Rick Bolton, 1989 (Box I:11, Folder 7)
  - Excommunication -- Steve Evans, Circa 1989 (Box I:11, Folder 8)
  - Excommunication -- The Jewish Museum, 1987-1989 (Box I:11, Folder 9)
  - Excommunication -- Hillary Leone, Circa 1989 (Box I:11, Folder 10)
  - Excommunication -- Bernice Steinbaum Gallery, Circa 1989 (Box I:11, Folder 11)
  - Excommunication -- Mitra Tabrizian, 1989 (Box I:11, Folder 12)
  - Excommunication -- Mark Wallinger (Anthony Reynolds Gallery), 1986-1988 (Box I:11, Folder 13)
  - Excommunication -- Press, 1989 November-1990 January (Box I:11, Folder 14)
  - Excommunication -- Miscellaneous, 1986-1989 (Box I:11, Folder 15)
  - Judite Dos Santos -- Aids Project (Missing/Desaparecidos), 1988-1989 (Box I:11, Folder 16)
  - Myrel Chernick, 1989 January-July (Box I:11, Folder 17)
  - Hujar -- Timeline and Biograpahy, 1989 November (Box I:11, Folder 18)
  - Hujar -- List, Undated (Box I:11, Folder 19)
  - Hujar -- Catalogue, 1989-1990 (Box I:11, Folder 20)
  - Hujar -- Press Releases, 1990 January 16 (Box I:11, Folder 21)
  - Hujar -- Press (1 of 2), 1991 February (Box I:11, Folder 22)
  - Hujar -- Press (2 of 2), 1990 February-September (Box I:11, Folder 23)
  - Hujar -- Press Photos, 1990 February-1991 June (Box I:11, Folder 24)
  - Hujar -- Mounted Image, Undated (Box I:11, Folder 25)
  - Hujar -- Traveling Exhibition, 1990 January-July (Box I:11, Folder 26)
  - Gernard Richter -- Background, 1990 (Box I:11, Folder 27)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Correspondence, 1989 September-1990 February (Box I:11, Folder 28)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Catalogue, Circa 1989-1990 (Box I:11, Folder 29)
  - Gerhard Richter -- ICA and Other Venues, 1989 August-1990 February (Box I:11, Folder 30)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Press (1 of 3), 1989 February-December (Box I:11, Folder 31)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Press (2 of 3), 1989 November-1990 October (Box I:11, Folder 32)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Press (3 of 3), 1989 May-1990 October (Box I:11, Folder 33)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Publicity Packet, 1989-1990 (Box I:11, Folder 34)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Reviews (1 of 2), 1990 March-1995 July (Box I:11, Folder 35)
  - Gerhard Richter -- Reviews (2 of 2), 1990 April-1995 July (Box I:11, Folder 36)
  - Barbara Strasen, 1990 February-May (Box I:11, Folder 37)
  - Paysage Demoralise: Landscape at the End of the Century -- Condition, 1990 May (Box I:11, Folder 38)
  - Paysage Demoralise -- Press Release and Publicity, 1990 April (Box I:11, Folder 39)
  - Paysage Demoralise -- Press, 1990 June (Box I:11, Folder 40)
  - Paysage Demoralise -- Helen Chadwick, 1987-1990 (Box I:11, Folder 41)
  - Paysage Demoralise -- Graeme Murray Gallery/John Weber, Findlay, Goldsworthy, Cooper, 1987 August-1990 April (Box I:11, Folder 42)
  - Paysage Demoralise -- Miscellaneous, 1987-1990 (Box I:11, Folder 43)
  - Peter Sebok -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Paysage Demoralise, 1 of 2), 1989 (Box I:11, Folder 44)
  - Peter Sebok -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Paysage Demoralise, 2 of 2), 1989-1992 (Box I:11, Folder 45)
  - Against Nature: Japanese Art in the Eighties -- Proposal, 1987-1988 (Box I:11, Folder 46)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Catalogue and Exhibit Roundtable Discussion, Circa 1989-1990 (Box I:11, Folder 47)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Labels, Circa 1989-1990 (Box I:11, Folder 48)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Color Xeroxes, Circa 1988-1990 (Box I:11, Folder 49)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Initial Schedule and Slide List, Circa 1989-1990 (Box I:11, Folder 50)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Installation, 1990 (Box I:11, Folder 51)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- John's Installation Notes, 1989 March-June (Box I:11, Folder 52)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- General Unnamed Sheets (Lists), 1989 January-June (Box I:11, Folder 53)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Dumb Type (1 of 2), 1988 June-1991 September (Box I:11, Folder 54)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Dumb Type (2 of 2), 1988 July-1991 April (Box I:11, Folder 55)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Dumbtype Correspondence, 1989 September-October (Box I:11, Folder 56)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Dumb Type "PH" VHS, 1990 (Box I:12, Folder 1)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Press Releases, 1990 August 16 (Box I:12, Folder 2)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Press Photos Information, 1989 July-1991 January (Box I:12, Folder 3)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Toshikatu Endo, 1987-1990 (Box I:12, Folder 4)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Shoko Maemoto, 1990 January (Box I:12, Folder 5)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Masami Teraoka, 1990 (Box I:12, Folder 6)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Noboru Tsubaki, 1986 (Box I:12, Folder 7)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Press, 1988-1990 (Box I:12, Folder 8)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Press Information, 1989 January-June (Box I:12, Folder 9)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Akron Art Museum Press, 1989 July-December (Box I:12, Folder 10)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Boston Press, 1989 December (Box I:12, Folder 11)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Grey Gallery Press (1 of 2), 1990 June-October (Box I:12, Folder 12)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Grey Gallery Press (2 of 2), 1990 September-1991 February (Box I:12, Folder 13)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- San Francisco Press, 1989 March-July (Box I:12, Folder 14)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Reviews and Notices, 1988 June-1990 August (Box I:12, Folder 15)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Akron Art Museum, 1989 September-October (Box I:12, Folder 16)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Contemporary Art Museum, Houston (Miscellaneous), 1990 October-December (Box I:12, Folder 17)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Seattle Art Museum, 1990 March-May (Box I:12, Folder 18)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Yasumasa Morimura, 1991 September-1992 April (Box I:12, Folder 19)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Japan Society News, 1988 March-November (Box I:12, Folder 20)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Miscellaneous Artist and Exhibit Material, 1986-1990 (Box I:12, Folder 21)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Miscellaneous Clippings (1 of 2), 1987 April-1989 July (Box I:12, Folder 22)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Miscellaneous Clippings (2 of 2), 1983 June-1988 November (Box I:12, Folder 23)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Miscellaneous Printed Material (1 of 2), 1983-1988 (Box I:12, Folder 24)
  - Against Nature (Japan) -- Miscellaneous Printed Material (2 of 2), 1958-1988 (Box I:12, Folder 25)
  - The Greeks and the Sea (Small Gallery, Nov. 12-20, 1990) (Box I:12, Folder 26)
  - Mabou Mines -- Preliminary Work, Circa 1980-1991 (Box I:12, Folder 27)
  - Mabou Mines -- Installation, 1990 October-1991 January (Box I:12, Folder 28)
  - Mabou Mines -- Drafts, Labels and Other Miscellaneous, 1976-1991 (Box I:12, Folder 29)
  - Mabou Mines -- Video Sleeve, 1990 (Box I:12, Folder 30)
  - Mabou Mines -- Press (1 of 2), 1980 December-1990 December (Box I:12, Folder 31)
  - Mabou Mines -- Press (2 of 2), 1990 May (Box I:12, Folder 32)
  - Tom Wolf and Ken Chu (Small Gallery/WSW), Circa 1990-1991 (Box I:12, Folder 33)
  - Mark Wallinger (Capital) -- Installation, 1990-1991 (Box I:12, Folder 34)
  - Mark Wallinger (Capital) -- Press, 1991 January-February (Box I:12, Folder 35)
  - Mark Wallinger (Capital) -- Miscellaneous, Circa 1990-1991 (Box I:12, Folder 36)
  - Minnette Lehmann, 1988 January-1991 January (Box I:12, Folder 37)
  - Permanent Collection, Circa 1990-1991 (Box I:12, Folder 38)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Checklists, 1991 (Box I:12, Folder 39)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Artists, 1990-1992 (Box I:12, Folder 40)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Artists CV's, 1991 (Box I:12, Folder 41)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Rasheed Araeen, 1991 June (Box I:12, Folder 42)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Rebecca Belmore, Circa 1990-1991 (Box I:12, Folder 43)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Nadine Chan, 1991 January-1992 October (Box I:12, Folder 44)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Albert Chong, 1991 June-November (Box I:12, Folder 45)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Allan DeSouza, Circa 1991-1993 (Box I:12, Folder 46)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Jamelie Hassan, 1991 February-1993 May (Box I:12, Folder 47)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Mona Hatoum, 1990 January-1993 April (Box I:12, Folder 48)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Roshini Kempadoo, 1991 January-July (Box I:12, Folder 49)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Glenn Ligon/Emily Fisher Landay, 1991 June-1992 (Box I:12, Folder 50)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Whitfield Lovell, 1990 December-Circa 1992 (Box I:12, Folder 51)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Lani Maestro, 1991 February-1993 April (Box I:12, Folder 52)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Lillian Mulero, 1990 December-1991 January (Box I:12, Folder 53)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Ming Mur-Ray, 1990 December-1992 April (Box I:12, Folder 54)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Keith Piper, 1990 January-October (Box I:12, Folder 55)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Ingrid Pollard, 1990 November-1992 October (Box I:12, Folder 56)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Donald Rodney/Art Council Collection, 1991 July-December (Box I:12, Folder 57)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Yinka Shonibare, 1990 October 19 (Box I:12, Folder 58)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Simmons/Janelle Reiring Metro Pictures, 1989 December-1990 April (Box I:12, Folder 59)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Black Artists File, 1985-1990 (Box I:13, Folder 1)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists, 1989-1990 (Box I:13, Folder 2)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists (In Show), 1985 April-1991 September (Box I:13, Folder 3)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists (Not Included), 1990 June-December (Box I:13, Folder 4)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists (Mulero), 1991 (Box I:13, Folder 5)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists (Gary Simmons), 1989 December-1990 August (Box I:13, Folder 6)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- American Artists (Glenn Ligon), 1991 July 29 (Box I:13, Folder 7)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- English Artists, 1988-1991 October (Box I:13, Folder 8)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- English Artists (Rasheed Araaen), 1990 November-1992 October (Box I:13, Folder 9)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- English Artists (Roshini Kempadoo), 1990-1991 (Box I:13, Folder 10)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Canadian Artists (Jamilie Hassan), 1984-1990 (Box I:13, Folder 11)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Canadian Artists (Lani Maestro), 1988-1991 (Box I:13, Folder 12)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Canadian Artists (Rejections), 1990-1991 (Box I:13, Folder 13)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Toronto/Halifax Notes, Lists and Other Miscellaneous, 1990-1991 (Box I:13, Folder 14)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- English Artists (Keith Piper), 1990 August-1991 January (Box I:13, Folder 15)